Translated by Releska
The sky of the blue sea
The time of the day and time of the day is
The day of the day when the light of the night rises
You and you and you
If you love me,
I'll be the one who'll be able to meet you
I'll be the one who'll be able to get along with you
Oh, this is false.
You'll never understand that.
You've been deeply checking out your own TV.
So amazing that you've lost your way.
We had a great time in your world.
I don't know where you are.
I don't know where you'll be back the most.
I'm not bored with anything.
It feels nice to be with my friends around me as well as your family.
I was looking forward to this world!
Rock, paper, scissors, two
What? What? What?
I can't go to the wrong place!
I'm not!
If you're not the right person, I'm not!
Oh! I'm not!
I'm not!
I can't do this!
No way!
So what's the game today?
This is it!
Wow, it's big!
I like it!
I found it before!
I took five of them!
It's small!
I found it before!
That's right!
That's not it!
I got it!
It's a pity when it's like this!
The children of Takugaiya Elementary School
came to solve such a problem
What?
What is it?
It's the best!
I'll do it after I did it!
This is it!
Did you do it?
It's the best!
Ta-da!
Let's go home!
Oh!
I'll do my best to get you out of here tonight!
Oh, I see.
I'm going to get you out of here tonight.
I'm so happy to see you.
I'm not going to get you out of here first.
But why do you want me to meet you like that?
You're not going to get me out of here?
If I were to meet you outside,
I wouldn't be able to hear the sound of the sea.
Why?
Your mother was like that.
You're not going to get me out of here?
Get lost!
You're not going to get me out of here tonight.
Let's get it started.
That's it!
I'm coming!
I'm looking for a new shop.
Have you found one?
Too bad...
So you're pretty crazy...
It's really worth it.
What are you doing with the two of them?
We're looking for a house. The big town.
Do you know where you're going?
I do. Isn't it cool?
I can find a house.
I went to the town where my parents were in this house.
Is that so?
Yes.
I was one of the people in the village.
So I thought that everyone was in trouble.
That's why I made this town.
Hmm?
I'm waiting!
I told you not to go back again.
What is this?
Is this my present?
I really don't think so.
Is this your present?
What?
I must have cropped something important.
I didn't expect it to be a disease at that shop.
What cropped something?
I don't know what cropped something about the matchmaking.
It's an bizarre thing to say, at least.
But you can show your girlfriend.
It's you!
What do you mean it's a grand Gate?
I don't know anything about it, but that's a very simple thing.
It's simple.
It's a five-storey building.
It's a building of the
Iarling's shoulders and the flowers.
I'm not a big fan of you.
I'm a big fan of you.
Well, it's good for you to be in the middle of the sun.
Hey, let's go to sleep, Ranko.
Ranko-san, what are you saying?
That's right! We're not looking for you!
I'm sorry! I was just kidding!
I'm sorry, Ranko-san.
It's my first time doing this.
Hello! How are you?
Hey, this is my chocolate.
Why did you come to me?
I can't help it!
I don't know!
It's a disease.
That's why I didn't want to come.
I told my mother to take care of me.
I'm not going to sleep any more.
Wow, Ranko-san's favorite tarako-san.
I'm sorry, but I don't eat well.
I feel like I'm looking at the face of Shiketa.
It's too bad, Tomokita.
Let's go home.
I don't eat well, it's strange.
That's really a disease.
It's okay if I just eat it.
It's too late to wake up.
I thought I'd ask for something.
Let's go!
I think we're going to have a lot of fun today.
What are you two doing?
Let's go!
What's wrong?
What? What's that?
A shopping cart.
You're different from the other one.
I'm a loser.
A shopping cart?
What?
I'm not going to eat it.
The shopping cart is here.
The shopping cart is a place where you can find something to eat.
I'm not going to eat it.
What's wrong with you?
I'm not going to eat it all.
What is wrong with you?
What are you two doing?
Don't go
Oh, it's over there.
Oh, it's over there!
It's over there!
I'll be able to keep it for a while.
Oh, it's over there!
It's the first time that I can't say it's over there!
If you all get along well, I'll be happy!
Oh, it's over there!
Can you hear the feeling of something?
Oh, it's over there.
I'll be able to keep it for a while.
Do you know how to keep it?
I have a certificate for being a member of the Human.
I have a certificate of being a member of the Human.
Of course, it can be a member of the Human.
I was able to show my charm to the other members,
who had to go on a meeting with their members.
I was able to keep it for that purpose.
But that's what I lost to the most important weapon!
I can't stand it anymore! I can't stand it anymore!
Everyone, are you looking for me?
No! Don't say that! I'm the boss of Super-Trendy!
I've been hiding in the dark for so long!
No! I can't stand it anymore!
I can't stand it anymore! I can't stand it anymore!
Is that the important weapon?
No way! It's not the most important weapon!
Maybe...
I've been fighting with this guy for five years!
I'm looking for something to buy!
No! Today, I'm going to protect you!
What do you mean?
It's a small black color, isn't it?
It has a black color, and it's a black color!
Really?
It's a black color, isn't it?
Yes, it's a black color.
It's a black color that protects you!
I don't know why...
I've never tried black color!
Look, I've never tried black color!
It's a black color that protects you!
I've never tried!
I've never tried black color!
You are always looking for me!
It's good to walk on this side now!
It's sweet, Mocha, and so many!
Thank you very much.
Please forgive me for all the things you've done.
Mr. Ranko!
I wish you all the best!
Yes, sir.
Please go to the doctor.
I'll take care of it.
I'll take care of it as much as I can.
Oh, is that you?
Is that you?
That's right.
It's important.
Hurry up.
There's no way here.
What?
Where are you going?
Mr. Ranko, I'm begging you.
I'm just going to take care of you.
Mr. Ranko, you're so handsome.
That's right.
Mr. Ranko?
Oh, if you were to help me,
you'd have to talk to Mr. Ranko
as if you were in the living room.
That's what I was saying.
So, where are you going to protect me?
If you don't have anything to do, I'll do it, Mr. Ranko.
What?
Who are you?
I did it all by myself.
Mr. Ranko, stop!
I'm going to take care of you.
I'm begging you!
What's wrong with Mr. Ranko?
What do you think?
Oh, I see.
I think Mr. Ranko is going to take care of you.
What? You too?
Mr. Ranko is a woman, so I can't let you down.
Mr. Ranko, you're going to take care of me.
Mr. Ranko!
What's wrong with you, Mr. Ranko?
Anyway, let's search for Mr. Ranko.
Mr. Ranko, you're going to take care of me.
Hey!
Mr. Ranko, stop!
Hey, Mr. Ranko, stop.
Oh, that's a bit of a hassle!
Oh, that's a hassle!
I'm going to go out to eat some water, so we're going to have a bite!
Oh, my! Wait a minute, I'm...
Here!
Here it is!
What?
Huh?
It's my mom!
No, no...
Hold my legs!
Oh, my, I might have been a bit more foolish.
Ah, I'm going to do it again.
I'm going to do it again.
Yaki!
I'm going to do it again and again and again.
Ah, it's hot.
I'm going to do it again.
Ah, that's...
Ah, you looked at this crap.
How could I know what's happening.
I don't think it's a funny thing.
I'm going to die.
What?
Are you crazy?
A movie or what...
That's what I...
I'm asking my own people.
It's real crap.
Please tell me.
That's crazy.
くうくく海
Mmm? But what?
カビカビ
うんうんうん!
それはいい考えね!
これやってもいいわ!
謎謎遊びにつき合ってくれたらいいね!
なぞ謎?
それでは第一問!
Ushitoriwa tolinga goisou taberました!
みんながもっと食べるように言ったら
意識はなんて言ったでしょ!
そゃあ!
くぐぐぐぐ!
It's not time to say goodbye to you!
You'll have to nail yourself with that sandal.
Wait! I'm not getting answer all the time!
What a nice way you can win this prize!
What?
You'll have to nail yourself with that sandal!
Well, yeah, I think there's plenty of potential for going behind, I guess.
It's a big problem, but I can't help it.
I can't stop it.
I'm sure it's going to be a big problem.
Oh!
It's almost done!
Hey, hey!
I'm glad!
Muka Muka!
I'll take you to the store!
No!
Hey, hey!
I can't go!
If I take it, it's the store's thing.
Oh, no!
I took my precious memory!
I was able to do it!
That's right!
Then, let's decide what to do.
Muka Muka!
My!
My memory!
I found it!
Thank you!
Muka Muka!
I'm glad!
It's been a while, Muka Muka.
It's been a while, Muka.
Why are you so old?
It's your birthday.
I came back to the store, but I didn't say anything.
That's why I'm so old.
I wonder if I can do it.
What are you doing?
I'm still tired.
Muka Muka Muka is not here today.
You're not here today?
I'm not here today.
It's a blunder.
What?
I'm just a little tired.
It's been a while since this kind of thing happened.
How about you, Kajiwihikunan?
That's right.
I thought you were really energetic yesterday.
I was busy with my private life.
I just went to the store and went to the store.
And I was running.
I just went now.
I was on the store.
Please!
Yes.
That's...
Hey! Then, I'm going to protect you.
You're still protecting me, aren't you?
Hey, you're so cruel!
Let's go.
※The others should never think of that.
This is...
Oh.
There's no way I'd possibly ever see such a big thing.
приходement is turning to me.
Huh?
That's why I got to wait for this.
Yes.
This is the one you got today.
I really don't have a chance to eat.
Banana, it's a banana.
This is bananas.
Ah, that's right, that's one more thing. I don't know if I should go to the ice cream shop, but...
Oh!
Ah!
No, I don't want to go to the ice cream shop when I go to the ice cream shop.
It's a shop.
I thought I'd go to the ice cream shop, but I think it's pretty good.
Thank you for your help.
I won't let you go to the ice cream shop. I'll go to the ice cream shop.
Ah, I'm going to get a bath.
I'm going to go home.
If you're going to get a bath, I'll do this and I'll do my best.
Oh, I hear the sound of the waves.
Do you want to hear it?
How do you hear it?
I hear it, too.
I heard the sound of the waves, and it was true.
There it is! There it is!
There it is!
Ah, wait. What's the game for today?
We can't find the entrance to the ice cream shop.
If you can find it, you can find it.
I don't think I like it.
Well, let's go to the ice cream shop.
Yes, let's go.
Let's go to the ice cream shop.
There it is!
Good luck, Good luck!
Good luck, bad luck, bad luck.
I hear it, I hear it, I hear it!
I don't know who was it,
and I'm going to the ice cream shop again.
I will go home.
As you are listening to the lights,
I still have the feeling that I would sleep in.
I will sing the song,
The hero who will sing the song.
I really like the girls beauty
was hearts
Bye
Let's try
let's do it
Let's do it
Everyone, boys
like us
I look forward to doing that
So lets start playing
Apppřom
Alright
I am getting ready
What is it!?
Eubinya-san brought a cat.
It's the boss who brought the cat.
We are in the same position.
It seems like a dragon came into the garden to help us out from the front.
What? It's a button to hold the body?
Yes, I'm going to do it.
Next time, I'll be in the front of the home cafe.
See you next time!